Bembo fatigue. Why are modern women so
immodest?
Cuz they get attention for it.
They get attention for it. And that's
why.
>> A relatively common experience growing
up, especially if you're a woman, is to
put your community's dress code to the
test. And when a violation of the code
occurs, the young woman is tempted to
ask, "Why?"
>> It's a fair question. Why do we have so
many rules about
>> time in middle school girls back. "Why
can't I wear this? WHY CAN'T I WEAR I
REMEMBER.
>> what people can or can't wear? And why
does there seem to be special emphasis
for this for women?
>> Unfortunately, the most common
explanation is because it will distract
the men and give them dirty thoughts.
>> Yeah.
>> Not only is this not the full picture,
in most cases, it's a flat-out lie. Many
women simply do not have the beauty
required to genuinely cause that.
>> Yeah, nobody wants to have a fat [__]
in a bikini.
>> Actually, if an effect does occur, it
will likely be men averting their gaze
in a reaction more akin to disgust at
being flashed than admiration. Do not
confuse something being eye-catching for
something being attractive. It's also
hard not to gawk at car accidents,
moles, and strange insects. This answer
also suffers
>> Yeah.
>> from another issue. It externalizes
responsibility. It claims that the
reason a woman can't dress the way she
wants is because the men can't control
themselves. And so, she has to take
responsibility on men's behalf. It's not
her moral failing that she's dressed
immodestly, but men's moral failing,
which she's expected to cover for. This
obviously breeds resentment and feminist
tendencies in the minds of young women.
>> That's right.
>> the real reason women must dress
modestly? And why does society do
everything in its power to obscure that
fact? That is this video's topic.
>> I'm actually curious what his answer for
this is. I'm actually I I I don't I
don't I like an answer in my head about
this. I'm actually super curious.
>> Consider to subscribe me. Helps the
channel.
>> [music]
>> Your attire serves two purposes,
function and communication. Function is
simply what your attire allows you to
do.
>> Yeah.
>> For example, heavy coats that withstand
the cold better. There's also obviously
a social function as clothes can make
you stand out to others. The type of
beauty can differ. Elegant wear invokes
admiration and immodest wear invokes
sexual attention. Some people trick
themselves into saying that they dress
up for themselves.
>> No.
>> others. They want to look more
attractive for their own self-esteem.
This is obviously false because if it
were true, they would dress the same at
home as they do in public.
>> But they don't.
>> Clearly in this scenario, their
self-esteem is dependent on how other
people see them.
>> Yeah, they want to be seen as hot and
they say they do it for themselves,
which is only partially true. They do it
so people see them as attractive.
>> Lastly,
>> That's true.
>> communication. Communication informs
others about you at a glance.
>> Yeah.
>> A police uniform implies a policeman.
>> Yep.
>> That's the point of a uniform. But it
goes beyond that. Mankind has long used
apparel to signify status, demonstrate
allegiance, express themselves, and even
identify threats.
>> Oh, oh.
>> For example, a man in a freshly pressed
shirt, combed hair, and suit is
considerably less likely to mug you in
an alley than someone in baggy clothes.
>> True.
>> Therefore, whenever someone chooses to
dress themselves in a certain way, we
are able to glimpse at two things. What
are they dressed to do and what are they
communicating about themselves by doing
so?
>> True.
That Yeah.
>> in mind, what information do we get from
a woman who chooses to dress immodestly?
>> That she's a [__]
>> First, let's look at function.
There's almost no gain in function with
immodest wear.
>> Yeah.
>> Not only are you exposing yourself to
the elements more without any utility,
it's hard to argue that most of these
modern attires can be classified as
comfortable. In fact, it's become common
nowadays that modern women cover up more
skin when at home simply because by your
clothes are more comfortable than when
they go outside.
>> Yeah, that's the usual. Like I mean, I
don't I've never been with a girl that
didn't do that.
Like they they walk around the house
like a [__]
uh
like one of those like sand people from
Star Wars
with like five [__] layers on.
>> Therefore, from the sacrifices in
function and comfort alone, we can
determine the following. The modestly
dressed woman must greatly value either
the communication her attire provides or
the increased sexual attention she
believes she'll get from strangers.
Otherwise, it would be illogical to make
those sacrifices in function and
comfort.
>> Yeah.
>> So, let's answer which it is. But before
I get into that, a quick word from
today's sponsor, the Rumble Wallet. As
the world's economic situation gets
dicier, bank users have to confront an
uncomfortable question. What if your
bank told you no to your own money?
Delays, transfers, frozen accounts. It's
been happening a lot. Crypto exists to
give you full control over your own
assets. But most people never try it
because they feel it's complicated.
That's where Rumble Wallet comes in. It
lets you buy crypto in minutes and cash
out whenever. And with MoonPay, you can
immediately buy cryptocurrency with your
credit card or bank transfers. [music]
And Rumble is offering a limited time
offer where you can start with $10 in US
stablecoin for free just by entering my
exclusive promo code.
>> This is why women become illogical. No,
when people are lied to, stimuli uh
respond to stimuli. So, what women do is
that they are stimulated by getting
positive male attention, so they
continue wearing clothes that gives them
positive male attention without
understanding that that positive male
attention is derived from their sexual
appeal.
>> Like a 10
>> effect. So, that's why that's a
confirmation
That's why I know what to
>> Terms and conditions apply. Details in
the description. Now, back to the video.
One of the obvious reason for a modest
wear is the attempt to get sexual
attention.
>> Yeah.
>> If a woman greatly values and is
attempting to get sexual attention from
strangers, either for self-validation or
for money, then she is often
And it makes sense why her family or
institutions would be against her
presenting herself that way.
>> But before we jump to conclusions, let's
analyze the communication angle. What is
a woman communicating when she violates
a standard of modesty and dresses in a
revealing manner? It depends partly on
the locals. Attire, similarly to
language, can be interpreted differently
depending on the situation. For example,
Western women who dress this way often
talk about liberation and how it's a
form of rebellion against antiquated
restrictive norms.
>> Uh-oh.
>> Meanwhile, in the Middle East and North
Africa, it's often interpreted as her
asking for trouble. A mismatch in this
form of communication can have some
unfortunate outcomes.
>> Yeah.
>> Feminists in the West have spent a lot
of time and energy trying to educate
their societies against the latter
interpretation, which is strange because
Western men aren't the ones using that
rationale or struggling with this issue.
But now that diversity is our strength
and we've mass imported peoples from
societies known for that exact mix-up.
>> There's a lot of people in different
cultures that think that if a woman is
dressed in a certain way, it means that
she's indirectly consenting to having
different things happen. Like maybe not
necessarily rape, but uh you know,
sexual uh you know, like behavior
towards her.
>> Different story.
>> Sexual harassment.
>> Naturally, if the purpose of revealing
attire is communicating liberation and
rebellion, it's doing a decidedly poor
job. Not only does the risk I
illustrated exist now in our world of
aspiring doctors and engineers,
rebellion also isn't what comes to mind
when someone dresses that way. When a
woman dresses immodestly, the word that
comes to mind is the very opposite.
>> Well, it's not really rebellion anymore
when every single pop singer is dressing
this way and acting like a [__] too.
I mean, like they're all doing it. So,
like how is everybody rebelling? If
everybody's rebelling, then it's not
really a rebellion anymore, is it?
>> It's conformity. It's what everyone else
is doing in modern society. Every
celebrity, every movie, every
commercial, and every video game.
>> That's That's what I was going to say.
Exactly.
>> a society where it's so normalized women
publicly expose themselves in waterproof
underwear at the beach or pool, and no
one bats an eye.
>> Sure.
>> Did you know that the inventor of the
bikini had to hire a stripper to debut
his invention because every model
refused to suffer the indignity at the
time?
>> Uh-huh.
>> And it makes sense. A bikini is
literally just underwear, and often more
revealing.
>> Sure.
>> opposed to being in public in one, but
not the other is an obvious
contradiction. When it comes to media
depicting women, there are only ever two
options. Either she's designed to be
lusted after, or she is made
deliberately ugly so as to not threaten
the self-esteem
>> theme of the women in HR. That's exactly
it.
>> On the other hand, modest beauty is
something far less common. If a woman
truly wanted to communicate a rejection
of societal norms, she would dress with
that ideal in mind. So, the
communicating liberation and rebellion
explanation is clearly defunct.
>> Well, the problem also is that like
nowadays, if you see girls that dress
that way, that act that way, you know
they're going to be a problem because
they have a chip on their shoulder.
That's another big issue that a lot of
these people have is they have a chip on
their shoulder, and they're constantly
trying to like fight against some sort
of perceived uh oppression that they're
experiencing in.
>> Before we throw out the communication
angle altogether, there is another
consideration.
>> Yeah.
>> Tribalism. Given that the modest wear
has become the norm, what if it is a
type of uniform to signal allegiance?
>> Yeah.
>> The theory is simple. Dressing
immodestly is a way for women to
communicate to other women that they
stand with feminist ideals of rebellion
against the patriarchy and that they
don't have internalized misogyny. That
way, even if they themselves don't want
to engage in attention-seeking behavior,
they're still giving the thumbs up to
the women who do, normalizing it, and
saying that they won't judge them for
it. And conversely, if you don't dress
like a
then society calls you approved of
internalized misogyny and you need to be
socially ostracized. You can see this
for yourself, whether in school or
university, public
>> like here's another angle of it is that
a lot of women that are okay with sex
work would be offended if you called
them a sex worker.
It's because they know that being a sex
worker is something that has a social
stigma and they don't like they
basically perform the action of thinking
that it's okay to be a sex worker, but
or like it's the same as like being a
trans a trans woman are real women,
okay. Well, but if you accidentally say
that they're a trans, they're going to
get offended. So, [snorts] it it's or
like, you know, Lizzo is beautiful. You
look like Lizzo, now you're sleeping on
the sofa. Like it it it's really just
performative morality. That's always
that's always what it is with people
like this.
Let's say saying you're a sex worker is
an insult. Yeah, like I mean, I love
[__] I think [__] are great. I I
don't see there being a problem with it.
But at the end of the day, that's what a
lot of these girls are and it's fine if
you want to do that. It's okay, but
that's still what you're doing. And
there's nothing wrong with that, but
just be just be who you want to be. I
think the issue that people have is that
they don't it's not enough for them to
live the way that they want. Everybody
else has to participate in the delusion
that it's not what it obviously is.
Whether it's trans stuff, whether it's
girls dressing in a certain way for
attention, whether it's OnlyFans. Like
at the end of the day, if you want to be
a prostitute, then be a prostitute, but
don't go and try to act and tell
everybody else that you're a business
owner. Like it's just misdirecting and
it's not
it's not understandable.
That's the Yeah, stop gaslighting us
about it. Yeah, people don't want to
live in a manufactured reality.
>> Nothing's etc. Even churches have this
issue of head coverings with women who
use them being treated as though they
think they're better than the others.
Even though head coverings were church
traditions for thousands of years. The
truth is simple. Modern women dress
immodestly because men reward them for
it and women punish them if they don't.
>> Mhm.
>> Breaking dress codes was marketed as
liberating women and giving them more
options. But if they choose decency,
they suffer consequences. It's a de
facto new dress code. Just one aimed to
please lustful men and opportunistic
women. How that can be called freedom is
beyond me.
>> There will always be about going and
doing it for attention. That's it. Yeah,
it'll be about doing things for
attention and it has always been about
doing things for attention. And it's
about signaling that you are part of the
end group. And there's also a lot of
people, too. Here's another big angle of
this. There are a lot I I I think there
are a lot of girls that used to be very
against booby streamers because they
were like, "Oh, well, these women take
away from our legitimacy as girl
gamers." And now they're like yass
queening every single girl that comes
out with an only fans. So,
fundamentally, I feel like it's just all
about a permission structure as with
everything. And there is no other sort
of ideology behind it other than just
signaling that you're being part of the
end group. That's literally it. That's
the only thing it ever has been. So,
yeah, that's it. Now, I feel like it's
very, very annoying, right? And it's
getting way too Christian This is
getting way too Christian for me. Well,
like, but it's true though, right? I
mean, that's the reason why girls dress
that way. Like, why else do you think
they're dressing that way?
Yeah, [snorts] like, what do you mean?
Like, it it's pretty [__] obvious,
isn't it?
Yeah, I I I I don't know.
I think it's super obvious. And uh many
female streamers back in the days hated
booby streamers and a few years later
they launched their only fans and then
they they promote it. Well, a lot of
these girls like like one thing that
girls love to do is they love to engage
in PvP without acting like they're
flagged for PvP. That is like the prime
female behavior that we see all the
time, which is like, "Oh, yeah, I'm just
asking questions or whatever." But
you're actually talking [__] about
somebody, but you're hiding behind this
like vague term for it, right? Let me
link this to you guys one more time.